I had thought of going to some school and secretly
eating the laddus of 15th August, but here
instead of laddus I got beaten with sticks.  Hello, yes brother, I want to
eat laddus on 15th August but how will I
eat them?  We don't even go to school.
Hey brother, come to the school behind my house, we will
eat laddus together, but yes, no one should get
suspicious.
Okay brother, I'll be back soon.
Do you want to eat laddus?  Come here.
Yes, bring it mom.
Mom, hit me with one more.   I have started
irritating everyone so much.  Hey friend, there are a
lot of children.  We will get the laddus only by entering among them.
Here is your packet of laddus
and this is your packet.  But you
both don't seem to be from our school.
[music]